Wet look lace and pearls? Yes please! Nohandmade reached out to me and asked
if I want to show some pieces of their new collection and I said yes! So today
I'm doing a quick try on haul because I haven't worn them yet and you can tag
along so let's get started. It's a cute little outfit a bodysuit later I'm
showing the catsuit version of that but for now it is the bodysuit with
suspenders and I love the look with the crisscross here in the stocking holders
suspenders I am not familiar with these words as you can tell because normally I
just wear catsuits and leggings but lingerie not so much so my English is a
bit rusty here. Okay the lace is really soft it's kind of like a velvety lace
which is really cool and it's totally stretchy so size adjustable so to say
and it has a crotch zipper just for the fun of it I guess because the bodysuit
is a bit more versatile than catsuit legs. And I have another no handmade piece I
already own for a longer while I want to come try and combine it because I think
it looks cool so it's this coat if you want to go outside and think this is too naked and
just get rid of the coat again at an event or something this is also an
option. Honestly you can't see the outfit underneath anymore but yeah when you arrive
somewhere just do it like this.
I'll get rid of it completely and then you're ready to party. So I think this is
really really cute and I guess this is going to be cute as well it's a really
short black dress and I'm going to change I think this is the
representation of a little black dress because it's very short and there's not
much material but it still looks great at least in my opinion and I also love
the chain here in the back which glitters so it's a bit of sparkle that's
why I also opted for this choker. I thought about wearing tights but then
you would have seen the waistband of the tights here because it sits so snug so I
said no tights today so you can like admire that really really smooth look
here and I love that kind of wet look fabric because it's just so comfy but it
still looks awesome. As for the cleavage here we have this kind of waterfall cut
out so it moves around a bit I just put it like this but yeah you can definitely
have different variations here. I totally love this one it's really cute it's
definitely like the one before outfit it's more for summer or indoors because
right now we have minus 60 degrees Celsius outside and I would not wear this anywhere
that's not 20 degrees plus.
Cute! I have to say I just love this back cutout
But I still have one more outfit to go, this catsuit.
So I'm going to change again.
I thought I'd start with the cloak again because I really dig this look, kind of.
And you can see already here that it's a bit more fetishy with the leggings underneath.
But the real outfit is of course the catsuit underneath.
I think you can still find the cloak online at some shops because it is from a previous
collection.
This is a catsuit version of the first outfit, the bodysuit.
I think it's also really cool.
It is definitely more dressed than the bodysuit.
So you have the whole leg part, the black wet look instead of some tights or fishnets.
I think I can't even decide between the two it's two totally completely different looks
um depends where I go I guess the first one is more lingerie and this one is more fetishy so
I like both and the dress also really handy again we have a cross zipper yay thanks no handmade for
this gimmick I think we girls really appreciate it anyway tell me in the
comments which one was your favorite I honestly love all three of them and they
will be a nice addition to my already big no handmade collection okay I hope
you had a nice time with today's video check out my other videos on my channel
join my patreon if you want to leave a thumbs up for this video thanks again to
know handmade for sending these over and I guess I'll see you in the next video
bye